hello everyone this is Rahul Zaria from
sherka welcome back to exciting 3
actionable stock updates 3 basically
means right sector right quality and
right valuation these are our investment
ideas today we have an update on HDFC
Bank our analyst maintains bu rating on
HDFC bank with the price target of R
2,000 quarter 2 of fi25 numbers were
broadly on expected lines with strong
deposit growth deposit growth would
continue to outpace loan growth in the
near term which should bring down the
ldr to normalized level fi25 and f26
would be the years of transition the
bank is confident of regaining its
growth trajectory and Nim once this
transition period is complete we remain
assertive from medium to long-term
perspective at the current market price
the stock trades at 2.2 times it's fi25
and 1.9 times it's fi 26 core Book value
estimates the stock has underperformed
the broader indexes in last 12 months
next we cover ICA
Lombard o analyst maintains buy rating
on icsa Lombard with a price target of R
2550 Quarter Two performance was in line
it is confident of retaining
underwriting performance despite higher
combined ratio at the industry level we
believe the company's healthy premium
market share along with focus on
balancing growth and risk selection
using data analytics to a profitable
growth is the right strategy we expect
icsa Lombard to deliver an Roe of 18 to
20% over the medium term at the current
market price the stock trades at 32.1
time at fi 26 and 28.4 times at fi 27
EPS estimate the stock has outperformed
the broader indexes in last 12
months investment in Securities Market
are subject to Market risks read all the
related documents carefully before
investing